<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<jobs><job><id>352f1d615dee4cbfae6b74795052900f</id><title>Registered Nurse - Resource Pool</title><company>The University of Vermont Health Network</company><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unit Description:&lt;/b&gt; RNs will float to the following areas below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;R5 - Oncology&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;R6 - Orthopedics, Trauma and Stroke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;R7 - Geriatric/Memory Care Unit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional training will need to be obtained to float to Progressive Care - R3/R4 (critical care), Psychiatry, and Women and Children's units.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Available Shifts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nights (Full Time)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;1 Day (Full Time)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;1 Evening (Full Time)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;No Per Diem Positions&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;On-call:&lt;/b&gt;  Not required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Incentives:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;$10K RN Sign-On Bonus for full-time. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Current RN licensure recognized by the State of New York required.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Appropriate experience in specific clinical area. Varies by unit.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Total Rewards Package includes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Health Care (Medical, Dental, Vision)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Account&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Retirement Benefits (403b)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Insurance Benefits (Life, Long-Term, Short-Term)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Paid time Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joining our team has its perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We encourage professional growth and development&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We ensure our nurses are truly happy and feel valued&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We offer structured preceptorships and continuing education&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We are committed to great patient ratios&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Our team culture is unlike what you'll find at other hospitals&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We've made significant investments in safe patient handling and mobility equipment&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Nurses truly have a voice here through our shared governance&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Area:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            The Champlain Valley is characterized by its working landscapes; undulating hills, meadows and pastures rolling down to the waters of giant Lake Champlain, the largest lake in the U.S. behind the Great Lakes. Plattsburgh, a picturesque community of 38,000, offers a cost of living just below the national average. The perfect place to raise a family, the area features excellent schools both public and private. The State University of New York also has a branch here with 6,200 students boasting a large international population and solid nursing program. Site Selection Magazine has chosen Plattsburgh as a top city in the nation for business development for the past eight years.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            In addition, Policom Corp has ranked Plattsburgh as the top micropolitan in New York and the 27th in the nation. As far as recreational opportunities, Plattsburgh and the Champlain Valley offer incredible year-round activities. From boating, biking, and fishing in the summer, to skiing and ice skating in the winter months. Nearby Lake Placid, host of the 1980 Winter Olympics and 2023 FISU World University Games, is a hub for recreation. The historic Strand Theater serves as the anchor of downtown Plattsburgh, and dozens of museums and historic attractions share the region's rich history.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            With exciting relocation and signing incentives and assistance, moving to upstate New York has never been an easier decision.
            &lt;/p&gt;</description><apply_url>https://api.collabwork.com/api:1SHNakFf/xmljobs?ref=MzUyZjFkNjE1ZGVlNGNiZmFlNmI3NDc5NTA1MjkwMGZ8MzcxZmQ3YzQtODlmZS00MTJjLWI1ZTUtNDFkNmYxNTZlNjhh</apply_url><employment_type>Part-time</employment_type><industry>Health Care Providers &amp; Services</industry><city>Plattsburgh</city><region>NY</region><country>US</country><remote>false</remote><salary><min>10000</min><max>10000</max><period>yearly</period></salary><posted_at>2025-08-06T17:00:00-07:00</posted_at><company_logo>https://img.logo.dev/ech.org?token=pk_LYubz9xdRXylW7gJL-T55Q</company_logo></job><job><id>0ed70d19a02e458782c3c9d22071851e</id><title>Registered Nurse - Women and Children's Unit</title><company>The University of Vermont Health Network</company><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unit Description: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Women and Children’s Unit at CVMC is proud to have the mission of providing ‘collaborative, high-quality, family-centered care’. You would be joining our growing multidisciplinary team of board certified OBGYN’s, Certified Nurse Midwives, experienced labor and delivery nurses, lactation consultants and perinatal technicians. Our unit’s leadership works hard to provide a dynamic environment that supports both the professional and personal growth and development of all members of our team.  The Women and Children’s Unit consists of 4 LDRP suites with labor tubs, 6 additional inpatient rooms, 3 observation rooms and a fully equipped Operating Room.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;On-call: &lt;/b&gt;Required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Incentives: &lt;/b&gt;$10K RN Sign-On Bonus for full-time (pro-rated for &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;part-time). Additional&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; terms &amp; conditions apply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Links:&lt;/b&gt; Check out our CVMC Women and Children’s Unit video: &lt;a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=dNWn_IneG8c&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and our webpage: &lt;a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;https://www.cvmc.org/departments-programs/womens-health-services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Current RN licensure recognized by the State of Vermont required.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Appropriate experience in specific clinical area. Varies by unit.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Total Rewards Package includes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Health Care (Medical, Dental, Vision)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Account&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Retirement Benefits (403b)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Insurance Benefits (Life, Long-Term, Short-Term)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Paid time Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joining our team has its perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We encourage professional growth and development&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We ensure our nurses are truly happy and feel valued&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We offer structured preceptorships and continuing education&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We are committed to great patient ratios&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Our team culture is unlike what you'll find at other hospitals&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We've made significant investments in safe patient handling and mobility equipment&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Nurses truly have a voice here through our shared governance&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the area:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Berlin, VT, located centrally in Vermont, is just minutes from the capital city, Montpelier. Our historical downtown areas feature a wonderful and unique assortment of local shopping opportunities, not to mention the many farmers' markets, pick-your-own-fields and community supported agriculture programs (CSAs).
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Within a state that boasts 52 state parks, 800 lakes and over 7,000 miles of rivers and streams, you'll find an abundance of opportunities for hiking, skiing, camping, fishing, sailing, swimming and more.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            If you're planning to relocate with your family in tow, Vermont is known for its high-quality public education and its well-established private schools. And whether you've always envisioned living in an old farmhouse or a historic Victorian, or building your dream house with your family, Vermont has plenty of real estate opportunities.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            With exciting signing incentives and relocation assistance, moving to Vermont has never been an easier decision.
            &lt;/p&gt;</description><apply_url>https://api.collabwork.com/api:1SHNakFf/xmljobs?ref=MGVkNzBkMTlhMDJlNDU4NzgyYzNjOWQyMjA3MTg1MWV8MzcxZmQ3YzQtODlmZS00MTJjLWI1ZTUtNDFkNmYxNTZlNjhh</apply_url><employment_type>Part-time</employment_type><industry>Health Care Providers &amp; Services</industry><city>Berlin</city><region>VT</region><country>US</country><remote>false</remote><salary><min>10000</min><max>10000</max><period>yearly</period></salary><posted_at>2025-08-06T17:00:00-07:00</posted_at><company_logo>https://img.logo.dev/ech.org?token=pk_LYubz9xdRXylW7gJL-T55Q</company_logo></job><job><id>1e96292af97540b3b4dcd1603a7aa086</id><title>Registered Nurse - Med/Surg</title><company>The University of Vermont Health Network</company><description>&lt;p&gt;The Registered Professional Nurse is responsible for the management of patient care, utilizing the nursing process to access, plan, implement and evaluate patient outcomes on the Inpatient Unit. Qualifications / Job Requirements:Education / Skills Required:• Graduate of an accredited nursing education program and holds a current license as a Registered Professional Nurse in NYS.• Previous experience as a Registered Professional Nurse preferred.• Must possess a high level of interpersonal skills to interact with patients, patient’s families, staff and management.• Must be highly motivated, able to work outside the normal working hours as volume demands.• As applicable, the individual has training, competency in attending to the special needs and/or behavior appropriate to the age of the patients for which care is being given.• Must possess the ability to collaborate with other health personnel.• Must have strong organizational skills&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Current RN licensure recognized by the State of New York required.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Appropriate experience in specific clinical area. Varies by unit.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Total Rewards Package includes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Health Care (Medical, Dental, Vision)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Account&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Retirement Benefits (403b)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Insurance Benefits (Life, Long-Term, Short-Term)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Paid time Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joining our team has its perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We encourage professional growth and development&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We ensure our nurses are truly happy and feel valued&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We offer structured preceptorships and continuing education&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We are committed to great patient ratios&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Our team culture is unlike what you'll find at other hospitals&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We've made significant investments in safe patient handling and mobility equipment&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Nurses truly have a voice here through our shared governance&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Area:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Elizabethtown, New York is a quaint, historic town in Essex County surrounded by the beautiful Adirondack Mountains and Lake Champlain. The area offers small town charm, recreational activities, and easy access to many area attractions.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Whether you are looking for adventure, escape, or spectacular scenery, you will find it in the Adirondacks. New York State's highest peaks have long been a draw for athletes, nature lovers and artists. Nearby Lake Champlain and the rolling Adirondack foothills offer scenic vistas and family-owned farms, in addition to sailing and paddling. To the west is Lake Placid, host of the 1980 Olympic Games and, more recently, the 2023 FISU World University Games. This focal point of upstate New York boasts amazing restaurants, premier shopping, and relaxing spas.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Elizabethtown is nestled between the Adirondack High Peaks and Lake Champlain. It is a family-friendly community with easy access to outdoor activities and nearby attractions. Hiking, cycling, and mountain biking; downhill, cross-country and backcountry skiing; rock and ice climbing; paddling, sailing and more are just minutes from your door.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            With exciting relocation and signing incentives and assistance, moving to upstate New York has never been an easier decision.
            &lt;/p&gt;</description><apply_url>https://api.collabwork.com/api:1SHNakFf/xmljobs?ref=MWU5NjI5MmFmOTc1NDBiM2I0ZGNkMTYwM2E3YWEwODZ8MzcxZmQ3YzQtODlmZS00MTJjLWI1ZTUtNDFkNmYxNTZlNjhh</apply_url><employment_type>Full-time</employment_type><industry>Health Care Providers &amp; Services</industry><city>Elizabethtown</city><region>NY</region><country>US</country><remote>false</remote><salary><min>250000</min><max>250000</max><period>yearly</period></salary><posted_at>2025-08-10T17:00:00-07:00</posted_at><company_logo>https://img.logo.dev/ech.org?token=pk_LYubz9xdRXylW7gJL-T55Q</company_logo></job><job><id>9153f417f8a34e7a82ccd93420ab1047</id><title>Registered Nurse - Helen Porter Nursing Home - Full time, Part time, or Per Diem</title><company>The University of Vermont Health Network</company><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unit Description: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Helen Porter Rehabilitation &amp; Nursing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Helen&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Porter Rehabilitation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&amp; Nursing is a welcoming, secure residence where loved ones are assured of skilled nursing care and assistance with daily living and where privacy is honored, and individuality respected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nestled in the farmlands of Middlebury, Helen Porter has accommodations for 98 people, is licensed by the state of Vermont and certified by Medicare and Medicaid. Helen Porter is a skilled and intermediate care residence which specializes in providing a home-like environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;We offer amazing benefits such as: &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sign on bonus up to $10,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Relocation bonus up to $9,200&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Health insurance, dental, vision, life, short and long term disability, family leave&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tuition discounts and reimbursements, certification reimbursements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Growth opportunities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive CTO program&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Referral bonuses for referring your friends &amp; previous colleagues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;We offer the following differentials in addition to the hourly rate of pay:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Per Diem $2/hour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Evening $3/hour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Night $5/hour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Weekend $2/hour (in addition to applicable shift differentials)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have 3 different units at Helen Porter, and you may apply to any of the 3 through this application. More information about the units below. Currently we have openings for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Full time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Part time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Per diem&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Long&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; Term Care Unit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;In addition to our many specialized services, Helen Porter continues to build upon our 30-year tradition of high-quality long-term care services. Separated from the Memory Care Neighborhood and the Short-Term Post Acute Rehabilitation Unit, our long-term care residents receive nursing care and assistance with daily living, as well as programs and activities tailored to their abilities and needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Memory Care&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; Unit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Memory Care Unit is designed to meet the changing needs of individuals as they experience the progression of symptoms and increases in cognitive loss associated with a diagnosis of dementia. Our early-stage program offers activity-based care in a warm, supportive and safe environment with a primary goal of helping individuals maintain dignity, purpose and functional ability. This highly specialized unit is staffed with very dedicated advocates and team members. Residents in this unit are the most vulnerable, usually unable to advocate for themselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Post Acute&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; Care - &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goal of the Post Acute Unit at Porter Medical Center - Helen Porter Rehabilitation &amp; Nursing is to provide supportive, goal-directed care following surgery and/or hospitalization. Specially designed treatment programs provide patients with the preparation, support and education that enables them to return home as quickly as possible. Our goal is to help patients reach their highest possible level of independence. A partial list of conditions we work with includes strokes, neurological conditions, orthopedic care, respiratory conditions, and cardiac and post-trauma situations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Routine Therapy services are provided Monday through Friday. We also have the capability of providing therapy six days a week if that is what is required to maximize positive results. Nursing staff provide the necessary extension of therapies when therapy staff are not present to provide direct service. This may include walking, exercises and supervision of other activities set up by the therapy staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;On-call: &lt;/b&gt;Not Required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Incentives: &lt;/b&gt;Up to a $10,000 sign-on bonus for full-time, pro-rated for part-time. Hourly Shift Differential: $3 Eve, $5 Night, $2 Weekend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Links: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.portermedical.org/helen_porter.htm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Current RN licensure recognized by the State of Vermont required.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Appropriate experience in specific clinical area. Varies by unit.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Total Rewards Package includes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Health Care (Medical, Dental, Vision)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Account&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Retirement Benefits (403b)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Insurance Benefits (Life, Long-Term, Short-Term)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Paid time Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joining our team has its perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We encourage professional growth and development&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We ensure our nurses are truly happy and feel valued&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We offer structured preceptorships and continuing education&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We are committed to great patient ratios&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Our team culture is unlike what you'll find at other hospitals&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We've made significant investments in safe patient handling and mobility equipment&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Nurses truly have a voice here through our shared governance&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Area&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Middlebury, VT is everything you'd expect in a quaint Vermont village—a white-steepled church, a Main Street lined with unique shops and a town green. Middlebury, VT is also home to world-renowned Middlebury College. We have a thriving arts scene with museums and art galleries as well as lectures, theater, music and dance performances. For those seeking adventure, Middlebury has the Green and Adirondack Mountains as our backdrops, offering limitless opportunities for hiking, biking, golfing, skiing, fishing and boating on nearby lakes and streams.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            With exciting signing incentives and relocation assistance, moving to Vermont has never been an easier decision.
            &lt;/p&gt;</description><apply_url>https://api.collabwork.com/api:1SHNakFf/xmljobs?ref=OTE1M2Y0MTdmOGEzNGU3YTgyY2NkOTM0MjBhYjEwNDd8MzcxZmQ3YzQtODlmZS00MTJjLWI1ZTUtNDFkNmYxNTZlNjhh</apply_url><employment_type>Part-time</employment_type><industry>Health Care Providers &amp; Services</industry><city>Middlebury</city><region>VT</region><country>US</country><remote>false</remote><salary><min>55000</min><max>75000</max><period>yearly</period></salary><posted_at>2025-08-08T17:00:00-07:00</posted_at><company_logo>https://img.logo.dev/ech.org?token=pk_LYubz9xdRXylW7gJL-T55Q</company_logo></job><job><id>0eca9543698d41529777eb3c784afff2</id><title>Registered Nurse - Operating Room</title><company>The University of Vermont Health Network</company><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unit Description: &lt;/b&gt;As a nurse in the Operating Room at The Central Vermont Medical Center you are working in a collaborative atmosphere. The operating room is open Monday through Friday seeing both inpatient and outpatient surgeries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;On-call: &lt;/b&gt;Required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Incentives: &lt;/b&gt;$10K RN Sign-On Bonus for full-time (pro-rated for part time).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Current RN licensure recognized by the State of Vermont required.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Appropriate experience in specific clinical area. Varies by unit.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Total Rewards Package includes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Health Care (Medical, Dental, Vision)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Flexible Spending Account&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Retirement Benefits (403b)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Insurance Benefits (Life, Long-Term, Short-Term)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Paid time Time Off&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joining our team has its perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We encourage professional growth and development&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We ensure our nurses are truly happy and feel valued&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We offer structured preceptorships and continuing education&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We are committed to great patient ratios&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Our team culture is unlike what you'll find at other hospitals&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;We've made significant investments in safe patient handling and mobility equipment&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Nurses truly have a voice here through our shared governance&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the area:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Berlin, VT, located centrally in Vermont, is just minutes from the capital city, Montpelier. Our historical downtown areas feature a wonderful and unique assortment of local shopping opportunities, not to mention the many farmers' markets, pick-your-own-fields and community supported agriculture programs (CSAs).
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Within a state that boasts 52 state parks, 800 lakes and over 7,000 miles of rivers and streams, you'll find an abundance of opportunities for hiking, skiing, camping, fishing, sailing, swimming and more.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            If you're planning to relocate with your family in tow, Vermont is known for its high-quality public education and its well-established private schools. And whether you've always envisioned living in an old farmhouse or a historic Victorian, or building your dream house with your family, Vermont has plenty of real estate opportunities.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            With exciting signing incentives and relocation assistance, moving to Vermont has never been an easier decision.
            &lt;/p&gt;</description><apply_url>https://api.collabwork.com/api:1SHNakFf/xmljobs?ref=MGVjYTk1NDM2OThkNDE1Mjk3NzdlYjNjNzg0YWZmZjJ8MzcxZmQ3YzQtODlmZS00MTJjLWI1ZTUtNDFkNmYxNTZlNjhh</apply_url><employment_type>Full-time</employment_type><industry>Health Care Providers &amp; Services</industry><city>Berlin</city><region>VT</region><country>US</country><remote>false</remote><salary><min>75000</min><max>95000</max><period>yearly</period></salary><posted_at>2025-08-10T17:00:00-07:00</posted_at><company_logo>https://img.logo.dev/ech.org?token=pk_LYubz9xdRXylW7gJL-T55Q</company_logo></job></jobs>